# ANDREA ARANDA

14909 sw 80th Street | Miami, FI | 786-762-1334 | aranda1822@gmail.com

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Highly experienced, adaptive, and attentive bartender with over ten years of experience in customer service and hospitality business. Impeccable work ethic and highly organized in a fast paced environment; seeking to apply mixology skills and create a following in a new and lively atmosphere.

#### SKILLS PROFILE

- Quick and efficient bartender
- Very accurate and extensive cash handling
- Able to make drinks with precision and style using both hands and multiple bottles
- Knowledge of traditional and modern drinks, as well as liquors, liqueurs, beers, and wines
- Experience in a variety of atmospheres including bars, restaurants, clubs and private parties (large and small) has put me at an advantage of acclimating to any and all environments with ease
- Expert at multi-tasking and using all senses while making drinks and taking care of my guests
- Extremely team oriented, yet can work just as well alone
- I have a following of regulars and can aid in establishing a following in any establishment

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

# Miller's Ale House

4/1/2010 — Present

### Palmetto Bay,FL

Server/Bartender: Responsible for serving food and drink orders while maintaining a clean work area.
 Carefully check all guests identification to ensure compliance of state alcohol regulations. Stay highly energized and ready to accommodate guest and server drinks. Certified training coach for servers and bartenders. Knowledge on liquor count and inventory.

#### Kitchen

June 2013 — June 2014

Miami Beach, FL

- Bartender: Responsible for ordering and signing off on inventory. Also responsible for training new bartenders and scheduling. Made all drinks including all specialties. Kept a high level of cleanliness in my own and others working areas. Promote drink specials and food specials for servers. Restocked all my own liquor and beer bottles.

#### Carnevale Restaurant

September 2008— June 2009

Miami Beach,FL

Server/Bartender: Responsible for numerous amounts of tables at a time at an in and outdoor
establishment. Kept everything polished and clean. Attained guests by selling daily food specials and
wine bottles. Trained behind the bar and made drinks for servers. Assisted guests from all over the
world in making drink and food choices. Delivered exceptional service by greeting and serving guests in
a timely and friendly manner.

Sam Goody/F.Y.E. - Sales Associate (January 2006-May 2007)

# The Sharper Image - Sales Associate (Holiday Season 2005 & 2006) Puccini & Pasta Italian Restaurant – (June 2005-January 2006)

# EDUCATION

- ABC Bartending school-2008: Graduated/ Certified Bartender
- Felix Varela Senior High School-2001-2005 :Graduated/ High school Diploma

# REFERENCES

- References upon request